toyshoponline.com.au 2019-03-04

# Terms and Conditions Toy Shop Online

By purchasing from this website you agree to the terms and conditions of the web store and in store. Prices on this website are in Australia Dollar **(AUD).**

We are committed to sourcing, creating and supplying innovative products that possess a diverse range. We are also committed to provide you with products of top quality that actually exceed the high expectations of customers. We are dedicated to providing information, advice and enthusiastic after-sales service to help you maximise your sales effort.

We welcome your feedback and suggestions as to how we can improve - and encourage you to contact us directly with comments on our existing products or ideas for additions to our range. We look forward to hearing from you.

## Dispatch

We normally dispatch from NSW but have various supplier distribution warehouse's accross Australia, Dispatch depending on the product purchased usually leaves the warehouse within 2 business days. Large Furniture items requiring a removilst may be between 2-7 days. A tracking number is emailed to you so you can follow it's transit progress and you can make arrangement to be at the delivery address.

## Change of Mind

Please choose carefully as refunds are not provided due to changed of mind, incorrect selection or if the item was found for a lower price elsewhere. We recommend you carefully preview your orders once added to your shopping cart before proceeding with checkout.

## Refund Policy

Should a refund be required, funds will be issued at the discretion of the relevant Toy Shop Online or PayPal. Refunds will normally be processed within seven (7) days.

Refunds will be returned to the same method of payment used to place the order should it be PayPal or Merchant facility. Under no circumstances will a refund be made to a different account.

**Shipping**

Shipping times vary depending on location, Dispatch and handling times will take up to 2 business days on online orders for items in stock, Should a product become out of stock we will notify you by phone or email within 2 days. 

We ship Australia wide . **Our prices on this website are in AUD**. The freight charges on the website are for Australian buyers only. We will not ship you item/s unless the correct shipping has been added to your final invoice. Toy Shop Online offer free transit insurance in compliance to the specified ‘goods damaged in transit’ conditions. With out sufficient evidence on the POD all claim will be denied.

It is your obligation to enter the correct delivery address details at time of ordering. If you enter the wrong address, we are not obliged to re-send the order to the correct address at our expense.

It is the responsibility of the customer to inform us if an order does not arrive. Once we learn if an order has not arrived by the due date, we will lodge enquiries with the courier to ensure delivery occurs as soon as possible.

The driver will leave a card advising the receiver that a delivery was attempted. The receiver is then to make contact directly with the courier to arrange another mutually convenient delivery date or collect from the closest depot. Re-Delivery charges may apply in the event you have been notified of the tracking number and dispatch date (your tracking number is in your account & also emailed)

Goods may be left but only if we are in receipt of written instructions from the buyer or receiver. These instructions can be included in the "Special Instructions" panel. **  _E.g. If not home leave behind side gate.  _**

Please note: if an item has been lost in transit, we will not dispatch a replacement item immediately. Replacement items will be dispatched according to our discretion. Without limiting the operation of any other Terms and Conditions herein, you agree that late delivery does not constitute a failure of our agreement, and does not entitle you to cancellation of an order.

Without limiting the operation of any other Terms and Conditions herein, we will not accept liability for any loss or damage arising from items lost, stolen or damaged after delivery has taken place. 

## Freight Charges

Freight charges are non refundable. Our delivery chargers re linked directly to our freight carrier for an immediate quote, Simply add the item/s to your shopping cart, view cart and click the estimate shipping button.

Buyers in some Western Australia locations, Rural area's and Northern Territory exceed normal freight charges within this website and will be required to pay prior to dispatch. We encourage you to request a quote prior to placing your order.

## Free Shipping

When an item is available for free shipping, free shipping is available solely for that particular item stated and no other's.

## Goods Damaged in Transit

All our items are covered by insurance however all items must be checked for damages on delivery. If item has been damaged must not sign any POD or documentation, and have the courier return it to Toy Shop Online. (If you cant check item/s before courier leaves please sign 'sight unseen'). Strictly No claims will be accepted if signed for. Requesting an ATL (authority to leave at address) voids any claims for loss and damage and should be referred to your own insurer. Signing the POD screen or docket states that the item has been received in good order and condition. If you do not sign and reject- to be sent back to us, we will gladly replace or refund your purchase once we have received the damaged item.

Damaged goods must be returned in the same condition as when received by you with all original packaging.

Under no cercumstances are goods to be returned without our consent which are outlined above. The goods will not be accepted at our dock should they not come back by the original carrier or packaging without prior agreement

## Pre-Orders

Products that are offered to pre-order, you will have the opportunity to secure the product by clicking the pre-order selection tab, A minimum 30% deposit will be required of the total value to secure with full balance due prior to dispatch. You can log into your account to pay installments leading to the due date. Once full payment is recieved the item will be dispatched within 2 business days.

## Contact

Where you have an queriy or issue relating to your order, please immediately contact us. Please have your invoice number on hand, along with the specifics of your order.

## Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy and are committed to handling your personal information in accordance with the Privacy Act 1988. This privacy policy explains how we manage your personal information that we collect about you. Please read this privacy policy before using the website at or submitting any personal information. By using the website, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the website to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

## Warrenty and Claims

Please note that goods must be returned within a reasonable period and you may be asked to demonstrate that the problem with the goods was not due to misuse. Consumer Guarantees do not apply where the goods became unacceptable due to fair wear and tear, misuse, failure to use the goods in accordance with manufacturer’s instructions, or failure to take reasonable care.

## Door to Door Service / Unsuccessful Deliveries

Our carriers provide a door to door service Only, due to OH & S regulations unless specified by Toy Shop Online.

You are responsible for the tracking of your item. An email will come through with your tracking number.

Missed Deliveries will receive a calling card for the receiver to contact the carrier and re-arrange delivery or depot collection. Re delivery fee's will be charged to the buyer if the item is returned to us by the carrier due to unsuccessful delivery attempt/s

Under no circumstances will you be refunded if the delivery has failed due to not being available and/or the product is returned to us

Removalist are used for larger pieces and are delivery charges on this website a for ground floor deliveries only. Charges may apply if the delivery address contains more than 3 steps, difficult access unpacking, repacking and or positioning.

A re-delivery with the removilist will be charged should the receiver miss the first attempt.

*Receiver means the address listed on your delivery docket

## Collection of Your Personal Information

Your personal information is not collected if you only browse this website.

We and/or our third party service providers may collect your personal information:

(a) directly from you;

(b) when you register as a member of the website;

(c) when you place an order via the website;

(d) where you access and interact with the website or the Team at Toy Shop Online; or

(e) from other sources.

The information collected may include your name, mailing or residential address, telephone number, email address and other transaction and registration details.

If you choose not to provide us with your personal information, we may not be able to provide the information, goods or the service you may require, or to fulfill one or more other purposes of collection of your personal information.

We do not collect your credit card or banking details as online payments are handled by PayPal and eWay. Please check their websites for details of their privacy policies and security measures.

## Our Use of Cookies

A cookie is a small piece of text that is placed within the memory of a computer and can be later retrieved by web page servers. We use cookies to enhance your interaction and convenience with our website and do not use cookies to record any personal information.

Cookies may record information about your visit, including the type of browser and operating system you use, the previous site you visited, your server’s IP address, the pages you access and the information downloaded by you. While this anonymous statistical data may be aggregated and used in broader statistical analysis by us and our web monitoring service provider to improve our services, at no time can we personally identify you as the source of that data.

## Use and Disclosure of Personal Information

You acknowledge and consent that by providing your personal information to us that we may use and disclose your personal information for the purposes for which it was collected or for a related or ancillary purpose such as:

(a) to Toy Shop Online to facilitate and process your order;

(b) to carry out or respond to your requests;

(c) to our third party service providers to assist us in providing and improving our services to you, and to analyze trends in sales and better understand our customer’s needs or to develop, improve and market our products and services to you;

(d) for regulatory reporting and compliance with our legal obligations;

(e) to various regulatory bodies and law enforcement officials and agencies to protect against fraud and for related security purposes;

(f) to our third party service providers to include in a database compiled by us or our third party service provider for use in direct marketing of promotions, product and services we think may interest to you;

(g) to seek your feedback in relation to customer satisfaction and our relationship with you;

(h) to our head office and its related bodies corporate for internal accounting and administration;

(i) to monitor or improve the quality and standard of service provided to you;

(j) to provide offers that may be of interest to you; and

(k) to better understand your preferences.

Our third party service providers are organizations that include those that may assist us with research, mail and delivery, security, professional advisory, banking, payment processing or technology services. Where we engage third party service providers to perform services for us those third parties may be required to handle your personal information. Under these circumstances those third parties must safeguard this information and must only use it for the purposes for which it was supplied, although we are not responsible for ensuring this.

Other than the above, we will not disclose your personal information without your consent unless disclosure is either necessary to prevent a threat to life or health, authorized or required by law, reasonably necessary to enforce the law or necessary to investigate a suspected unlawful activity.

Any permitted handling of personal information under any exemptions under the Act will take priority over this Privacy Policy to the extent of any inconsistency.

Providing Personal Information About Another Person

You represent to us that where you provide personal information to us about another person, you are authorized to provide that information to us, and that you will inform that person who we are, how we use and disclose their information, and that they can gain access to that information;

## Securing Your Personal Information

We have implemented appropriate physical, electronic and managerial security procedures in order to protect personal information from loss, misuse, alteration or destruction. Access to your personal information is limited to those who specifically need it to conduct their responsibilities.

We and our third party service providers take reasonable steps to destroy or permanently de-identify your personal information where it is no longer required and to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, disclosure, loss, misuse and alteration.

## Accuracy and Access to Personal Information

We take reasonable steps to ensure that the information we hold about you is accurate, complete and up-to-date. To assist us to do this, please provide us with the correct information and inform us if your details change. You may update your account details at any time by accessing your membership account or by contacting the Customer Care Team. If we deny you access to your personal information, we will provide you with the reason for such denial. We may recover from you our reasonable costs of supplying you with access to this information.

## Linked Sites

Toy Shop Online may contain links to websites, that are owned or operated by other parties. You should make your own enquiries as to the privacy policies of these parties. We are not responsible for information on, or the privacy practices of, such websites.

## Transmission of Your Data

Whilst care is taken to protect your personal information on the website, unfortunately no data transmission over the Internet is guaranteed as 100% secure. Accordingly, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you send to us or receive from us online. This is particularly true for information you send to us via email as we have no way of protecting that information until it reaches us. Once we receive your personal information, we are required to protect it in accordance with the Act.

## Website Hosting and Trans-Border data flows

Your personal information may be transferred to a database or server hosted within Australia, in which case, we and our third party service providers will comply with the trans-border data flow privacy standards under the Act, for example, by taking reasonable steps to protect the information being held, used or disclosed by the recipient inconsistently with the National Privacy Principles. Please let us know if you have any objections to such transfers.

## Changes to our Policy

From time to time it may be necessary for us to review and revise this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy at any time. Amendments or replacements of the Privacy Policy will be posted on the website.

## Direct Marketing

You consent to and authorize us to include your personal information in a database compiled by us for use in direct marketing by us. If you do not wish to receive marketing material from us, you can opt-out by contacting our sales team or by sending us an email. All emails, SMS and newsletters from this website allow you to opt-out of further mailings by clicking on the link “unsubscribe”.

## Interpretation

All defined terms in this Privacy Policy shall have the same meaning in this Privacy Policy as is given to those terms in the Terms and Conditions of this website.

By placing an order with Toy Shop Online you agree to the terms and condition. If you do not agree to the terms and conditions please leave our site immediately

## Our Privacy Complaint Process

If you are concerned with the way your personal information has been handled, please contact or write to us. If your personal information has not been handled in an appropriate way, we will take steps to remedy your concerns in a reasonable time. Please phone us or email your concerns. Toy Shop Online is an Australian business operated by Creative Wholesale Distributors.
